{
    "subject": "resource/WVAH-TV",
    "predicate": "ontology/locationCity",
    "object": "resource/West_Virginia",
    "human_readable": "WVAH-TV is located in West Virginia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9667075872421265,
            "question": "Where is WVAH-TV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9502041935920715,
            "question": "Can you watch WVAH-TV in West Virginia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8491493463516235,
            "question": "In which US state can you find WVAH-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8130845427513123,
            "question": "What is the name of the state where WVAH-TV broadcasts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8112213611602783,
            "question": "What region is associated with WVAH-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8070898056030273,
            "question": "Is WVAH-TV a television station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.785907506942749,
            "question": "What state is home to WVAH-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7804268598556519,
            "question": "Is WVAH-TV a local station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6315985918045044,
            "question": "What type of media outlet is WVAH-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295339822769165,
            "question": "Does WVAH-TV operate within the United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WVAH-TV is located in West Virginia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_418_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of media outlet is WVAH-TV?",
            "html": "dbpedia_418_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is WVAH-TV a local station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_418_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is home to WVAH-TV?",
            "html": "dbpedia_418_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_418_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide multiple mentions of WVAH-TV being a television station licensed to Charleston, West Virginia, and serving the Charleston\u2013Huntington television market. This information supports the triple that WVAH-TV is located in West Virginia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about WVAH-TV being licensed to Charleston, West Virginia, and serving the Charleston\u2013Huntington television market. This supports the statement that WVAH-TV is located in West Virginia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}